clickuplink.com 2012-12-31

# Click Up Link | Privacy Policy

Your privacy is very important to ClickUpLink.com. So, this is a bit more detail to help understand how the website will collect, use, communicate and disclose and make use of personal information. We will not rent, sell, lease, or give away any of your personal information. The following outlines our privacy policy. Please read this privacy policy before using the site or submitting any personal information. By using the site, you accept the practices described here.

(1.) Before or at the time of collecting personal information, we will identify the purposes for which information is being collected.  
(2.) We will collect and use of personal information solely with the objective of fulfilling those purposes specified by us and for other compatible purposes, unless we obtain the consent of the individual concerned or as required by law.  
(3.) We will only retain personal information as long as necessary for the fulfillment of those purposes.  
(4.) We will collect personal information by lawful and fair means and, where appropriate, with the knowledge or consent of the individual concerned.  
(5.) Personal data should be relevant to the purposes for which it is to be used, and, to the extent necessary for those purposes, should be accurate, complete, and up-to-date.  
(6.) We will protect personal information by reasonable security safeguards against loss or theft, as well as unauthorized access, disclosure, copying, use or modification.  
(7.) We will make readily available to customers information about our policies and practices relating to the management of personal information. 

## Cookie/Tracking Technology

We may use cookies and tracking technology which are useful for gathering information such as browser type and operating system, tracking the number of visitors to the site, and understanding how visitors use the Site. Personal information cannot be collected via cookies and other tracking technology, however, if you previously provided personally identifiable information, cookies may be tied to such information. Third parties such as our advertisers may also use cookies to collect information in the course of serving ads to you. Most web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer.

## Distribution of Information

We do not share your personally identifiable information to any third party for marketing purposes. However, we may share information with governmental agencies or other companies assisting us in fraud prevention or investigation. We may do so when: (1) permitted or required by law; or, (2) trying to protect against or prevent actual or potential fraud or unauthorized transactions; or, (3) investigating fraud which has already taken place.

## Commitment to Data Security

Your personally identifiable information is kept secure. Only authorized staff of this site (who have agreed to keep information secure and confidential) have access to this information. All emails and newsletters from this site allow you to opt out of further mailings.

## RSS and Email Subscriptions

This website records information about how people access our RSS feeds, but does not collect any personally identifying information from or about our RSS subscribers. This website's feed services collect the e-mail addresses of individuals that subscribe to our RSS feed via e-mail. Individual information about subscribers to this website's feed is held in strict confidence; we will not release or disclose any specific subscriber information under any circumstances, unless required by law. Aggregated information stripped of any personally identifiable information may be disclosed.

## Comments

Comments submitted to this website are the responsibility of the commenter. We reserve the right to remove or edit comments at our discretion. Site URLs (if provided) are published along with comments. E-mail addresses are required with the submission of comments but are not disclosed, unless the commenter deliberately does so him/herself by entering the e-mail address in the main comment box in addition to the box clearly labeled for the e-mail address.

ClickUpLink.com reserves the right to delete any comments that it deems not beneficial to the readership. This includes but is not limited to comments containing profanity, self promotion, harrassment, threats, or spam of any sort.

## External Links

The web site contains links to other websites not owned by the owner of this website. We will not, and cannot, control how your personal information is used on these other websites. Consult the privacy policies of the linked websites to see how they use your information

We reserve the right to make changes to this policy. You are encouraged to review the privacy policy whenever you visit the site to make sure that you understand how any personal information you provide will be used.
